<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ItApp</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome!"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="emaill">"@ucc.stu.edu.jm"</string>
    <string name="sendEmail">SendEmail</string>
    <string name="error_password">Password must contain at least 8 characters.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="type_your_email">Type your Email</string>
    <string name="type_your_password">Type Your Password</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="not_registered_yet_sign_up">Not Registered Yet , Sign Up !</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="re_password">Re-Password</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="already_registered_sign_in">Already Registered , Sign In !</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string-array name="faculty">
        <item>ROSE, Natalie</item>
        <item>DAVIDSON, Sonia</item>
        <item>AMONDE, Tom</item>
        <item>MILLER, Ionie</item>
        <item>NDAJAH, Peter</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="programe">The Bachelor Degree in Information Technology includes a rounded academic curriculum complemented by practical work. Skills are taught in a context that makes them transferable to the job environment and students demonstrate their readiness by completing projects that solve real world problems. The content and focus of the programme are constantly informed by current practice in the field through a participatory approach that includes input from our students, faculty, and advisory board. The curriculum reflects what is pertinent in the information technology industry and is a rigorous course that balances professional competencies and academic abilities.</string>

    <string name="entry">To be unconditionally admitted to complete UCC undergraduate programmes, individuals should possess a minimum of five (5) subjects at the GCE or CSEC level (including the mandatory English Language and Mathematics) at grades A, B, C or 1, 2, 3 respectively. A CSEC pass at level 3 must have been obtained since 1998.
Candidates who have a minimum of 4 CXCs can also apply pending the outstanding CXC subjects or can opt to do UCC replacement courses Core Mathematics, English for Academic Purpose and Fundamentals of Accounting.
Candidates can opt to apply under the Mature Entry option. To be accepted, applicants must be working for 5 years or more and be at a minimum age of 25 years. Academic qualifications, a detailed resume, a job letter and 3 professional references will be required.</string>

    <string name="mainpage">The University of the Commonwealth Caribbean (UCC) is registered with and recognised by the University Council of Jamaica (UCJ), the official accreditation body for tertiary education in Jamaica, as a University College. The University of the Commonwealth Caribbean has since achieved institutional accreditation by the UCJ. This positions the UCC as one of only five universities, of the eighty public &amp; private tertiary institutions that have been registered by the UCJ, to have achieved this significant &amp; decisive accreditation status.</string>

    <string name="footer">\nMAIN CAMPUS \n
17 Worthington Avenue, \n
Kingston 5, Jamaica W.I \n
(876) 906-3000 \n
    \nINTERNATIONAL ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICE \n
University of the Commonwealth Caribbean (UCC) / UCC Foundation US Inc. \n
Jacksonville, Florida, USA \n
interadminoffice@ucc.edu.jm \n</string>


</resources>